kshitiz saxena

designer/developer/programmer

EDUCATION

JAIPUR NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Master's of Computer Application
June 2017

RAJASTHAN UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Computer Application
June 2012

RAJASTHAN BOARD

Senior Secondary
April 2006

OBJECTIVE

I want to succeed in a stimulating and challenging environment, building the success of the company while I experience advancement opportunities.

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a designer, developer and programmer, specializing in webdevelopment, but with great interest to the AR/VR.

I am one of the very few self-driven and the fastest learner programmers with positive attitude. I will "NEVER SAY NO" to you. Somehow, I will find my way to do things.

EXPERIENCE

WEBCONTXT PVT. LTD. | LAL KOTHI, JAIPUR

Senior PHP Web Developer

Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

ADAPTATIVE PVT. LTD. | NIRMAN NAGAR, JAIPUR

Front End Developer Nov 2015 - Dec 2016

SYON INFOMEDIA PVT. LTD. | JAIPUR AIRPORT, JAIPUR

Web Developer Mar 2014 - Nov 2015 LANGUAGE

English Hindi

INTERESTS

Creative Writing

Audible books listening

Traveling Cricket **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

jQuery

PHP

MySQL

WordPress

Codeigniter

CakePHP

Shopify

Prestashop

PROJECTS

- 1. Worked on the Jaipur Literature Festival WordPress Website in 2013, 2017, and 2018. "https://jaipurliteraturefestival.org/"
- 2. Created a WordPress plugin in which content can be read when you like the page on Facebook and twitter. "Reveal me"
- 3. Made an Instagram hashtag printer. A product for Webcontxt. "Instagram Hashtag Printer"
- 4. Sound knowledge of SEO, Google Ads, and Landing Pages design.
- 5. Developing an application which is almost a replica of tinder. "Since Being Single"
- 6. Managed several projects at one time in Webcontxt. "Centre For Sight, Daiwa, Shinco, StoneX"
- 7. Shopify Website created and hit more than 85% website optimization in GTMatrix.
- 8. Listing website for canada's company in which listed all malls of canada from yellowpages api. "www.malled.ca"
- 9. Wordpress plugin to track utm-campaign for google ad words. "www.daiwa.in"
- 10. Wordpress payment gateway plugin created for a clothing company. "www.tgbi.mu"
- 11. Prestashop Payment Gateway Module Created for an american website.

CONTACT DETAILS

+91-9166332422 Near Gurjar Ki Thadi, Jaipur, Raj. - 302019 kshitizsaxena7@gmail.com